[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People suffering from pediophobia would be afraid of which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Cabbage patch kids", "incorrect_answers": ["Pregnant mothers", "Foot doctors", "Bicycles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1983 movie The Big Chill, which famous magazine did Michael work for?", "correct_answer": "People", "incorrect_answers": ["Time", "Newsweek", "Entertainment Weekly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which European country did the Dalmatian dog breed originate?", "correct_answer": "Croatia", "incorrect_answers": ["Netherlands", "Italy", "Denmark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which animal can be connected to a computer USB port?", "correct_answer": "Mouse", "incorrect_answers": ["Dog", "Rat", "Cat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Russia is the worlds largest country, with a land area of 17,098,242 square kilometers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1987 movie Dirty Dancing, Baby says she was named after whom?", "correct_answer": "the first woman in the cabinet", "incorrect_answers": ["the first woman to walk on the moon", "her mother", "the first woman to become president"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A worker at a Riverboat Casino in Ohio near Cincinnati gets off the late shift at 12 Midnight, and arrives home in Indiana at Midnight. This worker lives about an hour away. Is this possible?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term roasting is often used interchangeably with this word.", "correct_answer": "Baking", "incorrect_answers": ["Basting", "Braising", "Broiling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The author of the novel A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man is this writer.", "correct_answer": "James Joyce", "incorrect_answers": ["T. S. Eliot", "Samuel Beckett", "William Faulkner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which horror movie does the police discover that some mysterious deaths are linked to an Internet site whose every visitor dies in a horrible way?", "correct_answer": "Fear dot Com", "incorrect_answers": ["Sphere", "The Cubic", "Thirteenth Ghost"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is NOT a species of crocodile?", "correct_answer": "African Crocodile", "incorrect_answers": ["Nile Crocodile", "Mugger Crocodile", "American Crocodile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This U.S. automobile brand produces off-road vehicles, and was established in 1992.", "correct_answer": "Hummer", "incorrect_answers": ["Ram", "Jeep", "Maxwell"]}]